# JACKSON VU

# Web Development | Digital Marketing | Support

### CONTACT

Location: New York, NY Email: jackson10467@gmail.com Portfolio: www.JacksonVu.com LinkedIn: @JacksonVu Github: @Jackson10467

# **SUMMARY**

I am an eager Software Engineer/Digital Marketer/technology lover who is passionate about helping businesses and non-profits display forward thinking content to the users they support.

I seek the opportunity to work for an organization that places ongoing learning and development at the center of the employee experience.

# SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

HTML **CSS JavaScript** 

React.JS

Node.JS

**Express** 

Git

Github

MongoDB

Adobe Suite

Google Suite

Visual Design

Intercom

Jira

Salesforce

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Customer Support Engineer**

Reprise, January 2022 - Present New York, NY (Remote)

- Provided support to clients through Intercom with internal SLA targets prioritized
- Utilize HTML/CSS/JavaScript to troubleshoot customer reported issues and deliver solutions
- Initially triage incoming reported bugs to confirm reproducibility and potential causes before escalating to proper teams
- Created and reviewed both internal and customer-facing documentation to better define processes and enable customer success

# **Tier One Customer Support**

ExecOnline, July 2021 - December 2021 New York, NY (Remote)

- Provided support to C-Suite and management-level role customers as the first point of contact for support-related inquiries through Salesforce
- Referenced internal documentation to ensure consistent support
- Target SLA response times for efficient support experience

# **Software Engineering Fellow**

General Assembly, Feb 2019 - May 2020 New York, NY (Partially Remote)

- Participated in 500+ hours of applied training in software engineering and web development concepts focusing on frontend and backend development
- Built skills and fluency in HTML, JavaScript, Node, Express, and other web development frameworks
- Worked with UX Designers and Software Engineers to create full stack web applications

# **Digital Marketing Intern**

Webserves, May 2018 - April 2019 New York, NY

- Designed and launched marketing collateral using Adobe Suite
- Increased organizational membership by 20% through strategic partnerships and joint programming with technology non-profits
- Developed supporting blogs and visual content to increase audience engagement with organization website

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Hunter College (City University of New York)**

Bachelor of Arts (Emerging Media Studies) 2017 - 2019 | New York, NY

#### **General Assembly**

Certificate of Completion (Software Engineering Immersive) 2020 New York, NY